{
    "qas": [
        {
            "question": "Complete this phrase. As sick as a...",
            "choices": ["Penguin", "Parrot", "Puffin", "Partridge"],
            "answer": "Parrot"
        },

        {
            "question": "Which legal document states a person's wishes regarding the disposal of their property after death?",
            "choices": ["Will", "Shall", "Would", "Should"],
            "answer": "Will"
        },

        {
            "question": "Complete the title of the James Bond film The Man With The Golden...",
            "choices": ["Gun", "Tooth", "Delicious", "Eagle"],
            "answer": "Gun"
        },

        {
            "question": "Which of these fruits shares its name with something superior or desirable?",
            "choices": ["Apricot", "Mango", "Grapefruit", "Plum"],
            "answer": "Plum"
        },

        {
            "question": "In which sport do two teams pull at the opposite ends of a rope?",
            "choices": ["Ice hockey", "Basketball", "Tug of war", "Polo"],
            "answer": "Tug of war"
        },

        {
            "question": "Where would a cowboy wear his chaps?",
            "choices": ["On his hands", "On his arms", "On his legs", "On his head"],
            "answer": "On his legs"
        },

        {
            "question": "Which of these zodiac signs is not represented by an animal that grows horns?",
            "choices": ["Taurus", "Capricorn", "Aries", "Aquarius"],
            "answer": "Aquarius"
        },

        {
            "question": "Prime Minister Tony Blair was born in which country?",
            "choices": ["Northern Ireland", "Scotland", "England", "Wales"],
            "answer": "Scotland"
        },

        {
            "question": "Whose autobiography has the title A Long Walk To Freedom?",
            "choices": ["Ranulph Fiennes", "Nelson Mandela", "Mikhail Gorbachev", "Mother Teresa"],
            "answer": "Nelson Mandela"
        },

        {
            "question": "Duffle coats are named after a town in which country?",
            "choices": ["Germany", "Holland", "Belgium", "Austria"],
            "answer": "Belgium"
        },

        {
            "question": "Complete this stage instruction in Shakespeare's The Winter's Tale: 'Exit, pursued by a ...'",
            "choices": ["Dog", "Tiger", "Bear", "Clown"],
            "answer": "Bear"
        },

        {
            "question": "The young of which creature is known as a squab?",
            "choices": ["Octopus", "Pigeon", "Salmon", "Horse"],
            "answer": "Pigeon"
        },

        {
            "question": "Who is the patron saint of Spain?",
            "choices": ["St John", "St James", "St Peter", "St Benedict"],
            "answer": "St James"
        },

        {
            "question": "Which king was married to Eleanor of Aquitaine?",
            "choices": ["Henry I", "Henry V", "Henry II", "Richard I"],
            "answer": "Henry II"
        }
    ]
}